Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 75, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Slavery in the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Author: Tamiment Institute Library
- Box: 75, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Small Business and Government Regulation, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Report with Recommendations, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 9, 1950
  - Item 3: Materials in the National Archives Relating to Small Business, 1943; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. National Archives
    Notes: April 1943
  - Item 4: Small Business Problems, 1941; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 26, 1941
  - Item 5: Meeting the Special Problems of Small Business, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 1947
  - Item 6: Report of Proceedings, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Author: Conference of American Small Business Organizations
    Notes: February 18-20, 1947
  - Item 7: Report of Proceedings, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 2-4, 1948
- Box: 75, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Local Development Company Loans, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Author: Small Business Administration
    Notes: June 30, 1964
  - Item 2: Mobilization Guide for Small Business, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Author: U.S. Defense Production Administration
- Box: 75, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Topics for Small Business, 1961; Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Author: Montana State University
  - Item 2: Small Business and Foreign Trade, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Notes: April 6, 1964
  - Item 3: Mechanization and Automation in Small Business, Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Author: James M. Beauchamp
  - Item 4: Small Business in the American Economy, 1962; Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
    Author: U.S. President's Committee on Small Business
  - Item 5: A Survey of Federal Government Publications of Interest to Small Business, Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Box: 75, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Estates Programme in India, Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
    Author: India Ministry of Commerce & Industry
  - Item 2: The Opportunity of the Smaller Business, Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
    Author: Sentry Insurance
  - Item 3: Small Manufacturing Establishments, 1972; Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Box: 75, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Federal Government Publications of Interest to Small Business, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: List of Publications, 1963; Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
    Author: U.S. Select Committee on Small Business
- Box: 75, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Financing Small Business, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Notes: December 1950
  - Item 2: Local Development Company Loans, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 9)
    Author: U.S. Small Business Administration
    Notes: December 31, 1964
- Box: 75, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Selected Characteristics of the Small Business Wholesalers in the State of New Jersey, Publication (Box 75, Folder 10)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Conservation and Economic Development
- Box: 75, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Suggested Research Topics, 1961; Publication (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Box: 75, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Chemicals, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Box: 75, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Synergy as a Method for Coping with Change, Publication (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Box: 75, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The University and the New Priorities, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 14)
    Notes: November 11, 1968
- Box: 75, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Processes of Change, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 15)
    Author: Norman D. Kurland
- Box: 75, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Coping With Change, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 16)
    Notes: October 1, 1965
- Box: 75, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: First Things First, Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Author: Walter P. Reuther
  - Item 2: Design for Tomorrow, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 17)
    Author: International Association of Personnel Women
    Notes: May 9-11, 1968
- Box: 75, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Group Processes in Intergroup Education, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: Jean D. Grambs
  - Item 2: Group Dynamics and Education, Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: National Education Association
  - Item 3: Compulsory Sickness Insurance, 1920; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: National Civic Federation
    Notes: January 30, 1920
  - Item 4: Message of the President Recommending Legislation on Economic Security, 1935; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: January 17, 1935
  - Item 5: After the War: Toward Security, 1942; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: National Resources Planning Board
    Notes: September 1942
  - Item 6: Social Security Act Amendments, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Notes: June 2, 1948
  - Item 7: Social Security in the United States, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: The Social Security Program, 1936; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: Marietta Stevenson & Ralph E. Spear
    Notes: April 1, 1936
  - Item 9: What is Social Insurance?, 1935; Publication (Box 75, Folder 18)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Economic Security
- Box: 75, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Workers' Control and Administration of Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Jan Gallas
  - Item 2: The Fight for Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Henri Raynaud
  - Item 3: Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: ILO
  - Item 4: Fundamento del Derecho de Propiedad y Seguridad Social, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Manuel Bruned
  - Item 5: Soziale Sicherung und Landwirtschaftliche Bevolkerung, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Th. Bergmann
    Notes: November 1956
  - Item 6: Le Assicurazioni Sociali e la Loro Influenza Sull'Equilibrio del Sistema Economico, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Albertina Degli Oddi Alfieri
  - Item 7: Five Lectures on Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Edwin E. Witte
  - Item 8: The Objectives of Social Security, 1958; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Notes: December 28, 1958
  - Item 9: Social Security Abroad, 1949; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Henry W. Steinhaus
  - Item 10: Inducement of Benefits Under Social Insurance, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: Carl W. Strow
    Notes: September 1948
  - Item 11: Economic Security Among the States, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Bill Analysis, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: American Enterprise Association
    Notes: April 18, 1960
  - Item 13: Text of and Justifications for Amendments to H.R. 6675 Recommended by the Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Notes: June 3, 1965
  - Item 14: The Genesis of Social Security in America, Publication (Box 75, Folder 19)
    Author: J. Douglas Brown
- Box: 75, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Seguro Social: Su Teoria y Su Aplicacion en el Ecuador, 1963; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Anibal Campana Barrera
    Notes: July 1963
  - Item 2: Ligje, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Shtepia Botonjese
    Language: Albanian.
  - Item 3: Seguro Social: Su Teoria y su Aplicacion en el Ecuador, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Anibal Campana B.
  - Item 4: Social Services in Czechoslovakia, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: NSSO
  - Item 5: Seguridad Social de Cundinamarca, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Instituto de Seguridad Social
  - Item 6: Social Security Act, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Republic of Ghana
  - Item 7: Social Insurance for Salaried Employes in Austria, 1937; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Marianne Sakmann
    Notes: March 1937
  - Item 8: Administration Report of the Director of Social Services, 1949; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Ceylon Government Press
  - Item 9: A Unified Scheme of Social Insurance for Industrial Workers in India, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: V.P. Keni
  - Item 10: Extension of Social Security to Puerto Rico and the Virgin Islands, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Notes: February 6, 1950
  - Item 11: Outline of Social Insurance in Japan, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Japanese Social Insurance Agency
  - Item 12: Actuarial Report on Trust Territory Social Security System, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Robert J. Myers
  - Item 13: Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Summary of Social Insurance and Assistance Services, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Ireland Department of Social Welfare
    Language: English; Gaelic.
  - Item 15: Organizacao Corporativa e Previdencia Social, 1959; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Instituto Nacional de Estatistica
  - Item 16: La Previdenza Sociale in Agricoltura, 1959; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: La Rivista Italiana di Previdenza Sociale
  - Item 17: Memoria de las Labores Desarrolladas Durante el Segundo Periodo del Instituto de Seguridad Social, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Author: Departamento de Cundinamarca
  - Item 18: Law of Social Security in West Pakistan, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 19: For Future Social Security Benefits, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 20: Federal Social Security Tax Guide, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Notes: January 1, 1967
  - Item 21: Farm Rental Income, Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Item 22: Further Improvements Needed in Processing Widows' Claims for Black Lung Benefits, 1974; Publication (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Notes: December 31, 1974
- Box: 75, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Revised Social Pensions, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
    Author: Sheila Suttner
  - Item 2: Social Pensions in South Africa, Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Act, 1963; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
    Author: Republic of South Africa
    Language: English; Dutch.
  - Item 4: Act, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Act, 1962; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Act, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Act, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Act, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Act, 1961; Publication (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Box: 75, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Social Services, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Author: Australia Department of Social Services
  - Item 2: Social Services of the Commonwealth, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Commonwealth Social Services, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Joe Wheeler Finds a Job and Learns About Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Instructions for a Representative Payee, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Summary of Social Security Amendments of 1972, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Notes: October 17, 1972
  - Item 7: Socialinio Drudimo Pensijos ir Gydymas, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Author: Paulius Leonas
    Language: Lithuanian.
  - Item 8: Good News for Household Workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: Medicare, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: The Journal of Risk and Insurance, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Author: American Risk and Insurance Association
  - Item 11: History of the Provisions of Old-Age, Surivors, Disability, and Health Insurance, 1973; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Notes: February 1973
  - Item 12: History of the Provisions of Old-Age, Survivors, Disability, and Health Insurance, 1971; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Notes: June 1971
  - Item 13: Need to Strengthen Procedures for Determining Continued Eligibility of Widows for Federal Benefits, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 22)
    Notes: August 22, 1968
- Box: 75, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Rendement de la Perception des Cotisations de Securite Sociale, 1969; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Author: Office National de Securite Sociale
  - Item 2: Rendement van de Inning der Bijdragen van Sociale Zekerheid, 1969; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Author: Rijksdienst Voor Maatschappelijke Zekerheid
  - Item 3: Social Security for Wage-Earners, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Author: Ministry of Foreign Affairs and External Trade
    Notes: December 1970
  - Item 4: Social Security Special Benefits for People 72 or Over, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Social Security Programs in the United States, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Old-Age, Survivors, Disability, and Health Insurance, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Notes: January 2, 1968
  - Item 7: Old-Age, Survivors, Disability, and Health Insurance Provisions, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Notes: January 1968
  - Item 8: Rights and Responsibilities of Those Who Receive Social Security, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Notes: December 1965
  - Item 9: Cocial Security Amendments of 1971, Publication (Box 75, Folder 23)
    Notes: May 26, 1971
- Box: 75, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Legislacao da Previdencia Social Atualizada, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Author: Edicoes Trabalhistas
  - Item 2: Novo Regulamento da Previdencia Social, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: If You Work While You Get Social Security Payments, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Social Security: What it Means for the Parents of a Mentally Retarded Child, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Social Security Amendments of 1967, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: November 9, 1967
  - Item 6: Summary of Social Security Amendments of 1967, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: December 1967
  - Item 7: Summary of Social Security Amendments of 1967, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Social Security Amendments of 1967, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: November 8, 1967
  - Item 9: Social Security and Your Household Employee, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Your Social Security Earnings Record, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: How Social Security Works for Nonprofit Organizations and Their Employees, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Social Security Information for Crew Leaders and Farmers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Author: U.S. Treasury Department
  - Item 13: Social Security Credits, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 14: Social Security Information for Self Employed People, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: October 1964
  - Item 15: Social Security Amendments, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 16: Old-Age, Survivors, Disability, and Health Insurance Provisions, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 17: Social Security Amendments of 1969, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: December 5, 1969
  - Item 18: Social Security Amendments, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: December 14, 1970
  - Item 19: Social Security Amendments, 1971; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 20: What You Can Expect, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 21: The Future Role of Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Author: Tax Foundation
  - Item 22: Your Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 23: Your Social Security Earnings Record, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 24: Where to Get Help or Information on Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 25: Social Security Amendments, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Author: Commerce Clearing House
    Notes: August 25, 1964
  - Item 26: Social Security Amendments, 1965; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 27: Your New Social Security Benefits, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 28: Your New Social Security Benefits, 1956; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 29: The Social Security and Retirement Program, 1962; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Author: Ward W. Bauder, Otis Durant Duncan, James D. Tarver
    Notes: March 1962
  - Item 30: The Status of the Social Security Trust Funds, Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 31: Social Security Information, 1961; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Item 32: Social Security Amendments, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 24)
    Notes: September 9, 1964
- Box: 75, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Report of the California Social Insurance Commission, 1919; Publication (Box 75, Folder 25)
    Author: California Social Insurance Commission
    Notes: March 1919
  - Item 2: Assembly Interim Committee on Civil Service and State Personnel, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 25)
    Author: California Legislature
    Notes: December 1960
- Box: 75, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Clases Sociales y la Politica de Seguridad Social en Chile, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
    Author: Instituto de Administracion
  - Item 2: Continuidad a la Prevision, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 26)
    Author: Ediciones "Gutenberg"
- Box: 75, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Duluth Conference on Employment Security, 1950; Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    Author: University of Minnesota
    Notes: December 1-2, 1950
  - Item 2: Proceedings of the Social Security Conference, Publication (Box 75, Folder 27)
    Author: Michigan State University
- Box: 75, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: La Seguridad Social Como Disciplina: Naturaleza, Autonomia y Ensenanza, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
    Author: Carmelo Mesa Lago
  - Item 2: Una Nueva Etapa de la Seguridad Social Cubana, Publication (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Box: 75, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Cash Benefits in the Case of Illness, Disability, Accidents, Old Age, etc., Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    Author: Denmark Ministries of Labour and Social Affairs
  - Item 2: Outlines of the National Assistance Act, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Vore Sociale Rettigheder, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    Author: Idag
  - Item 4: Social Forsorg, Ulykkes- og Livsforsikring, Publication (Box 75, Folder 29)
    Author: Ungdommens Forsikrings Orientering
- Box: 75, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Social Security and Pension Practice in Western Europe, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    Author: International Pension Consultants
    Notes: July 1, 1966
  - Item 2: La Seguridad Social en el Mercado Comun Europeo, 1967; Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    Author: Carlos Maria Campos
    Notes: February 24, 1967
  - Item 3: Annexes to the European Interim Agreement on Social Security Schemes Relating to Old Age, Invalidity and Survivors and Protocol Thereto, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    Author: Council of Europe
    Notes: February 1, 1966
    Language: English; French.
  - Item 4: A Guide to Social Security in Western Europe, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    Author: Noble Lowndes International Limited
    Notes: July 1, 1968
  - Item 5: The Danish National Insurance Act, 1936; Publication (Box 75, Folder 30)
    Author: Sigurd Wechselmann
- Box: 75, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Soziale Sicherheit - Uberstaatliche Rechtsnormen, Zwischenstaatliche Vertrage, Publication (Box 75, Folder 31)
    Author: Sozialpolitik in Deutschland
- Box: 75, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Comparison of Social Security Expenditures in Canada, 1970; Publication (Box 75, Folder 32)
    Author: Department of National Health and Welfare
- Box: 75, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Social Security, Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
    Author: Ministere du Travail
  - Item 2: Liste des Organismes de Securite Sociale, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
    Author: Federation Nationale des Organismes de Securite Sociale
    Notes: February 1968
  - Item 3: Le Regime General de la Securite Sociale, 1949; Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
    Author: La Documentation Francaise
    Notes: September 22, 1949
  - Item 4: Sur un Regime Particulier d'Assurance Sociale, 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 33)
    Author: Said Zakaria
- Box: 76, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Will America Copy Germany's Mistakes?, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Gustav Hartz
  - Item 2: Socziale Sicherung in der Bundesrepublik Deutschland und in der Sowjetzone, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Bundesministerium fur Arbeit und Sozialordnung
  - Item 3: Was Geschiet mit den Beschwerden in der Sozialversicherung?, 1965; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Adolf Gabriel, Erwin Bunzel
  - Item 4: Die Familienkrankenpflege, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Heinz Thumler
  - Item 5: Rechtsprinzipien Sozialer Sicherung, 1967; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Walter Bogs
    Notes: October 18, 1967
  - Item 6: Zur Frage der Sozialen Sicherung Landwirtschaftlicher Familien in der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Bernd van Deenen Albert Harms
  - Item 7: Die Uberwachung der Beitragsentrichtung, 1963; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Author: Schewe
- Box: 76, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Everybody's Guide to National Insurance, 1964; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Pensions & National Insurance
  - Item 2: National Insurance Bill, 1954; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Planning, 1945; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: March 23, 1945
  - Item 4: National Insurance Act, 1946; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Alban Gordon
  - Item 5: Social Security: the New Priorities, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Keith Joseph
  - Item 6: Britain's Charter of Social Security, 1948; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: British Information Services
  - Item 7: Social Security in the 70's, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: The Young Conservatives
  - Item 8: Social Services in Britain, 1948; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: December 1948
  - Item 9: Social Insurance Proposals for Earnings-Related Short-Term and Invalidity Benefits, 1969; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Health and Social Security
  - Item 10: Social Services, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: W.K. Brennan
  - Item 11: Supplementary Benefits Handbook, 1971; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: April 1971
  - Item 12: Social Security in Britain, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Agreement on Social Security, 1966; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: National Superannuation and Social Insurance, 1969; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Social Security in Britain, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Earnings-Related Social Security, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Social Insurance, 1969; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)